活跃生命周期是指当你的Activity处于前台并且
The active life cycle is when your activity is in the foreground and
被显示在屏幕上。  此时Activity可以响应用户的事件  并且
has focus. Here it is actively receiving input from user events and
不会被其他Activity所遮挡  当 onPauses 调用时，
no other activities are obscuring it. onPauses hold and
active生命周期结束 并且那些显示activity被部分遮挡。
the active lifetime ends as soon as your activity is partially obscured,
像这个例子中  由于你选中了Google商店中的某个应用  查询对话框跳出
like in this example. [SOUND] You can see here the permissions dialogue
遮住了Google Play程序
is displayed in front of Google Play for
来安装这个应用  再例如  另一个Activity想要
an app in store. Or the same thing happens when you have another activity trying
执行一个隐式的Intent  并需要用户做出选择  所以
to fulfill an implicit intent and the user needs to make a selection. So
为了有效的利用有限的资源
to make efficient use of limited resources,
你会想要利用这些信号来调整自己的应用的资源占用情况
you'll want to use these signals to adjust your app's resource burden.
当活跃生命周期结束的时候  UI的交互可以暂停
So, most updates through a UI, can be paused when this lifetime ends,
这是通过onPause信号来传达的  但是你会看到  这个Activity还是可见的
which is announced by onPause. But as you see, the app is still visible, so
所以你不能暂停任何跟你的UI显示相关的进程
you shouldn't pause any processes that are drawing your UI. The visible
可视生命周期表示你的应用是可见的全程
lifetime on the other hand continues whenever the app is at all visible and
当你的应用被别的应用遮住时  可视生命周期结束  像这样
ends as soon as it's completely obscured by another app. Like this.
所以  一旦你看到onStop信号产生时  应用转到后台
[SOUND] At this point, our app is moved to the background.
用户就完全看不到你的应用了
So when you see onStop, you know the user can't see your app at all. So, while
当你的程序运行时  创建onCreate和销毁onDestroy大多数时候只会被调用一次
OnCreate and OnDestroy will be called at most once, each time your app is run,
但是这些事件(onStart,onStop,onResume,onPause)会被调用多次
these handlers are likely to be called many times, while the app is running.
这里就是不同的地方了  基本上所有的平台
Now, this is where things get a little different. On almost al platforms,
应用的生命周期都是可预测的  具体来说就是  你启动一个程序
app life cycles are deterministic. Generally, you'll start a program and
它持续的执行  知道程序结束或者用户点击取消
it'll keep running, until it either completes or the user cancels it. You look
你可以参考传统的桌面开发  你的程序一直保持运行  直到
at traditional desktop development that means your app keeps running until your
用户在文件菜单中点停止或者退出  这时你可以释放资源
user chooses quit or exit from the file menu. At that point you can say stay and
但是  Android的生命周期不同
free resources. But as we know on Android life cycles work a little differently.
让我们看看Android的生命周期到底是怎么工作的
So, let's take a closer look at exactly how that works now.